{
    "subject": "resource/RocknRolla",
    "predicate": "ontology/producer",
    "object": "resource/Guy_Ritchie",
    "human_readable": "RocknRolla was produced by Guy Ritchie.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.852084755897522,
            "question": "Which film was produced by Guy Ritchie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7247748374938965,
            "question": "Besides RocknRolla, what other films has Guy Ritchie directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7129125595092773,
            "question": "Name a movie produced by Guy Ritchie."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6615121960639954,
            "question": "What is the name of the producer who worked on RocknRolla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4876576066017151,
            "question": "What year was RocknRolla released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4062861502170563,
            "question": "What is the genre of RocknRolla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38366562128067017,
            "question": "Who directed the film RocknRolla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35370343923568726,
            "question": "What is the plot of RocknRolla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26815593242645264,
            "question": "Who are some of the main actors in RocknRolla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25004062056541443,
            "question": "Is there any common theme in Guy Ritchie's films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=RocknRolla was produced by Guy Ritchie.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2744_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of the main actors in RocknRolla?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2744_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of RocknRolla?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2744_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed the film RocknRolla?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2744_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2744_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2744_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2744_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2744_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2744_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2744_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2744_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2744_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2744_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2744_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents mention that Guy Ritchie directed \"RocknRolla\", there is no information about him being a producer of the film.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* There are multiple documents discussing the movie \"RocknRolla\" and its production team.\n* One of the documents mentions that \"Director Guy Ritchie achieved critical and financial success with his crime films \u2018Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels\u2019 in 1998, which was quickly followed up by in 2000 by \u2018Snatch\u2019. The films were both extremely tight with excellent scripts including well written dialogue, captivating characters and interesting plots set in the criminal underworld.\"\n* Another document mentions that \"RocknRolla\" is a 2008 gangster film directed by Guy Ritchie.\n\nHowever, I couldn't find any information that explicitly states \"Guy Ritchie produced RocknRolla\". The context suggests that he directed the movie, but doesn't mention production.\n\nTherefore:\n\n{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about Guy Ritchie being the producer of \"RocknRolla.\" The documents mention Guy Ritchie as the director of the film but do not provide details on his role in production."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several passages state Ritchie directed the film and wrote the story. The context implies a director usually isn't also the sole producer, though they can be. It's more common for separate individuals or production companies handle that role.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The passage states that \"Oh, wait, we know the answer to that \u2014 it was called \u2018Swept Away,\u2019 an unfortunate byproduct of his time with Madonna.\" which implies that Guy Ritchie's film \"RocknRolla\" is not a product of his own production but rather something he previously made in collaboration with another person (Madonna), thus suggesting that he didn't produce RocknRolla.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information describes Guy Ritchie as the director of RocknRolla, not the producer.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}